postquare.com 2019-03-22

# Postquare - Privacy

Welcome to the postquare.com. Postquare.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of our Postquare.com website (the "Site"). As such, we have established and implemented this privacy statement to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Site how we use and protect the information we collect. 

## What information does Postquare.com collect?

Postquare.com does not collect personally identifiable information unless our visitors voluntarily provide it to us. We do, however, collect certain types of information and ask for personal information in certain circumstances, such as when you set up an account. The following sections describe what type of information we collect, when we collect it and how we use it. In order to use certain functionality of the site, you will have to create a user account which requires you to submit certain personal information. When you register and create an account, we require you to provide us with the name of the web site, the name of the web site owner or administrator, and phone number. Upon activating an account, you will select a password. Your email address and password will be used so you can securely access and maintain your account. You may also be asked for personal information to access certain areas of the Site. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to a visitor’s hard drive to help tailor and keep records of his or her visit to the site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many web sites use them. Cookies allow web site operators to better customize visits to the site to the visitor’s individual preferences. We do not receive or record any personal information in the cookies we use. Although most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent that or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Even without accepting a cookie, you can still access the site. 

## Customer Service

We provide customer service support through email. In order to provide customer support, we will ask for your email address. Aside from this information, we do not ask for any personal information to provide customer support. We only use information received from customer support requests, including email addresses, for customer support services and we do not transfer or share this information with any third parties. 

## How do we use the information you provide us?

As stated above, we use your personal information such as your name, address, billing and mailing address and credit card number for billing purposes when we charge you for the use of your account. We also will use your email address to contact you when we provide customer support. In addition, from time to time, we may also use your email address to send you information on updates to the site, or if you choose to be included, to alert you to offerings from other companies that we are affiliated with. We will not ever sell your email address or send you offerings from companies that we are not affiliated with. We may also provide aggregated information about our visitors to outside parties from time to time. We may use the information we collect to tailor your experience through the site by displaying content according to your interests and preferences, providing a faster method for you to access your account and submit information to us and allowing us to contact you, if necessary. 

## How does Postquare.com protect customer information?

We implement a variety of security measures to ensure the security of your personal information on our systems. User personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to such systems. Any credit card information you supply us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology ("SSL") and HTTPS protocol and then stored into our databases to be accessed only as stated above. 

## Does Postquare.com disclose the information it collects from its visitors to outside parties?

Postquare.com does not currently sell, trade, or otherwise transfer outside the company personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily provide in any account registration. This information is used to better understand how visitors use the Site, to support related transactions made on the site, and to better know our visitors and possibly tailor any specific features, promotions, or other notifications to them. However, this data in an aggregate form without any personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Should you change your mind about the information you’ve provided to us, should you no longer wish to receive information from us, or should your information change, we have provided a way for you to correct, update or remove the personal data you gave us. In the event Postquare.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, visitors’ information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Visitors will be notified via prominent notice on the Site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of information of users held by us. If as a result of the business transition, information will be used for a purpose different from that stated, or implied, at the time of collection users will be given a choice consistent with our notification of changes section. Notwithstanding any other term of this privacy statement, we may release any personal information we obtain or collect when we believe its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. 

## How do you change the information we have for you?

To update, modify or delete the information that we have on file for your account, simply go to the "My Account" section of the Site, log in, then modify your details and settings as necessary. Please note that we require some personal information for billing purposes. If you wish to delete your name, telephone number, email address, billing or mailing address or credit card number, you will be required to terminate your account. 

## Third party links and co-brand relationships.

In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, we may choose various third party web sites to link to, and frame within, the Site or to display or promote as part of the site. We also participate in co-branding and other relationships to offer e-commerce and other services and features to our visitors. However, even if the third party is affiliated with us, we have no control over these linked sites, each of which has separate privacy and data collection practices independent of us. Data collected by our co-brand partners or third party web sites (even if offered on or through our site) may not be received by us. As such, we have no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such web sites. These linked sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the site and the links placed upon each of them and therefore request any feedback on not only the site, but for sites each links to as well (including if a specific link does not work). 

## Notification of changes.

By visiting the Site or using its features, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as set forth in this privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes within this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

## Questions? Contact us.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or your dealings with the site, please do not hesitate to contact us in the contact us page. 

## Terms and Conditions

Please also read the Terms of Use establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Site.
